And I click Create Image, and I Wait, and as you see,
after a pretty long time, after a pretty long wait,
we're having our images ready.
So it's not funny at all, because it has made it a cartoon-like image.
But whatever, so as you see, one of our credits are removed, or gone, so it's gone.
So right now, our 15 credits is now converted to 14.
And over here, as you see, we have two images created, and for each of them,
I can click on Edit, and I will be forwarded to the Image Editor part of Microsoft Designer.
And I am also able to click on Download, or what else do we have?
Uh-huh, it says Content, Crit and Sholes, generated with AI.
Both Confident, Information, about, hold on.
Okay, whatever.
And yes, this is what we got.
So we can also download or edit it, as you see.
I close this one, and this was the Image Generator of Microsoft Designer.